

PERSONAL DATA

- Date of Birth
 August 27th, 2002
- Place of Birth
 San Salvador, El Salvador
- Gender Male
- Marital Status
 Single

CONTACT

- @ vegaricardo636@gmail.com
- +503 7953-7389
- mricardomartinez.shop

MORE KNOWLEDGE

SQL PL/SQL Python

FastAPI JavaScript

Flask MySQL Django

NoSQL Tkinter

Json Pandas React

NumPy SQLalchemy

RICARDO MARTINEZ VEGA

PYTHON SOFTWARE ENGINEER

SAN SALVADOR, EL SALVADOR

Python Developer, with over 4 years of both professional and work experience. I have worked with various companies, applying my knowledge and development skills.

Work experiences focused on single-page or multi-page applications using different technologies such as Django, Django Rest Framework, Flask, and FastAPI, creating web platforms, custom backends, and adhering to best practices. Proficient in library usage for Data Structures such as Pandas or Numpy, AI libraries like TensorFlow, desktop interface libraries like Tkinter and QT, as well as database management including SQLAlchemy, MySQL, Oracle, SQL, NoSQL, MongoDB, and PostgreSQL.

ACADEMIC BACKGROUND

Fourth Year - Systems & Computing Engineering

Universidad Pedagogica De El Salvador

Master Course in Oracle: Oracle SQL, Oracle Apex, Oracle Forms, Discoverer Udemy Academy

Web Development Course: HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, Ajax, PHP, MySQL Udemy Academy

Responsive Web Design with Foundation for Sites SASS and XYGrid

React - The Complete Guide: Hooks, Context, Redux, MERN Udemy Academy

Udemy Academy

Master Course in Python: Python3, MySQL, Django, Flask and Tkinter Udemy Academy Ongoing

Finished

Finished

Finished

Finished

Finished

SKILLS

- Responsibility
- Problem-solving
- Communicative
- Teamwork
- Punctuality

LANGUAGES

- Español Native
- Inglés Intermediate

HOBBIES

- Reading
- Music and Arts
- Producer
- Technical Support
- Programmer

Master in CSS3 - Avanzado

Udemy Academy

Administration of VPS and production websites

Udemy Academy

WORK EXPERIENCE

Python Software Developer & DBA

Construmas S.A De C.V Febrero 2022 - Septiembre 2023

February 2022 - September 2023
Web programmer in Python, responsible for developing CRM systems for employees and clients, using the best front-end technologies such as HTML, CSS, JS + frameworks, and backend technologies such as Django and MySQL or MongoDB.

Systems administrator, DBA working with MySQL database managing databases, queries, tables, etc.

Oracle Software Developer

PersonalSoft September 2023 - Present

Oracle Developer, working with Oracle 11g database, Oracle Forms 11g and Oracle Forms 12C, SQL Developer, Oracle Discoverer, also involved in developing accounting and real estate applications in PL/SQL and Oracle Forms, working on obsolescence and scheduled changes.

Ongoing

Finished

Finished

Finalizado

REFERENCES

Kenny Martinez (Trainee)

TELUS International El Salvador

Cel: 6029-5567

Ingrid Mejia (General Treasurer)

Construmas S.A DE C.V

Cel: 7120-1010

Evelin Vega (Secretary)

Instituto Salvadoreño De Pensiones (ISP)

Cel: 7735-3910

Ricardo Martinez (Bachelor's graduate)

MInisterio De Educacion El Salvador

Cel: 7658-7411